export default {
  common_questions: 'Questions',
  common_answer: 'Answer',
  common_answers: 'Answers',
  common_stats: 'Stats',
  common_users: 'Users',
  common_popular: 'Popular',
  common_slidebar: 'Slidebar',
  common_points: 'Points',
  common_previous_step: 'Previous step',
  common_next: 'Next',
  common_bold: 'bold',
  common_and: 'and',
  common_italic: 'italic',
  common_check_out: 'Check out',
  common_title: 'Title',
  common_tags: 'Tags',
  common_for_exemple: 'For example',
  common_voted: 'Voted',
  common_oldest: 'Oldest',
  common_rencent: 'Recent',
  common_view_profile: 'View Profile',
  common_approve: 'Approve',
  common_reply: 'Reply',
  common_share: 'Share',
  common_report: 'Report',
  common_home: 'Home',
  common_asked: 'Asked',
  common_in: 'In',
  common_language: 'Language',
  common_views: 'Views',
  common_followers: 'Followers',
  common_name: 'Name',
  common_badges: 'Badges',
  common_beginner: 'Beginner',
  common_teacher: 'Teacher',
  common_top_members: 'Top members',
  common_login: 'Login',
  common_registre:'Sign Up',
  common_forgot_password: 'Forgot password',
  common_email: 'Email',
  common_password: 'Password',

  authentification_enter_your_email: 'Enter your email address to recover your password',
  authentification_reset_password: 'Reset password',
  authentification_back_to_login: 'Back to login',
  authentification_first_name: 'First Name',
  authentification_last_name: 'Last Name',
  authentification_confirm_password: 'Confirm Password',
  authentification_create_account: 'Create Account',
  authentification_remember_me: 'Remember Me',
  authentification_sign_up: 'Sign up',
  authentification_forgot_your_password: 'Forgot your password',
  authentification_donot_have_account: `Don't have an account?`,
  authentification_this_page_need_to_authenticate: 'This page need to authentificate to continue',
  authentification_: '',

  header_home: 'Home',
  header_about_us: 'About Us',
  header_contact_us: 'Contact Us',
  header_blog: 'Blog',
  header_user_profile: 'User Profile',
  header_edit_profile: 'Edit Profile',
  header_best_answers: 'Best Answers',
  header_logout: 'Logout',
  home_ask_a_question: 'Ask a Question',
  home_share_and_grow: "Share & grow the world's knowledge!",
  home_description: `We want to connect the people who have knowledge to the people who need it, to bring
  together people with different perspectives so they can understand each other better,
  and to empower everyone to share their knowledge.`,
  home_create_a_new_account: 'Create A New Account',

  nav_home: 'Home',
  nav_communities: 'Communities',
  nav_questions: 'Questions',
  nav_new_question: 'New Questions',
  nav_trending_question: 'Trending Questions',
  nav_must_read_question: 'Must read Questions',
  nav_hot_question: 'Hot Questions',
  nav_tags: 'Tags',
  nav_badges: 'Badges',
  nav_users: 'Users',
  nav_help: 'Help',
  nav_ask_a_question: 'Ask a question',
  nav_best_answers: 'Best Answers',
  nav_top_members: 'Top Members',

  question_tell_us_your_questions: 'Tell us more about your question',
  question_your_description:
    'Your description gives people the information they need to help you answer your question.',
  question_check_out_these_examples:
    'Check out these examples of great question descriptions',
  question_want_more_help: 'Want more help',
  question_review_question: 'Review your question',
  question_let_one_more_look: `Almost there! Let’s give your question one more look. And don’t worry—you can edit your question after it’s posted, too.`,
  question_check_for_typos:
    'Check for typos, slang, and text formatting issues',
  question_for_exemple: 'For example',
  question_format_text: 'Format your text with',
  question_donnot_include_slang: ` Don’t include slang or shorthand: “u can’t bc it's mine”`,
  question_these_tips_for_editing: 'these tips for editing with Markdown',
  question_for_guidance: 'for guidance',
  question_post_your_question: 'Post Your Question',
  question_what_your_programming: `What's your programming question? Be specific.`,
  question_what_languages_technologies:
    'What languages, technologies, and/or frameworks is your question about?',
  question_tags_help_the_right_people:
    'Tags help the right people find and answer your question.',
  question_identify_your_tags: `Identify your tags by completing the sentence, “My question is about…”`,
  question_include_tags_that:
    'Include tags that are crucial to your question only, like europe, us,...',
  question_only_included_in: 'Only included in the proposed scope',
  question_your_title_help:
    'Your title helps people quickly understand what your question is about so they can answer it.',
  question_imagine_you: `Imagine you’re asking a question to another developer.`,
  question_is_there_an_R: `“Is there an R function for finding the index of an element in a vector?”`,
  question_please_help_with_R: `“Please help with R”`,
  quetion_what_is_your_title: 'What’s your question title?',
  question_what_category_of_questions:
    'What category of questions do you want to ask?',
  question_we_will_help_you:
    "We'll help you find the best way to get your answer.",
  question_i_have_a_question_about: 'I have a question about studying',
  question_i_nedd_help_with: 'I need help with a working problem',
  question_i_nedd_to_troubleshoot: 'I need to troubleshoot some immigration',

  answer_best_answers: 'Best Answers',
  answer_leave_answer: 'Leave an answer',

  share_on_facebook: 'Share on Facebook',
  share_on_twitter: 'Share on Twitter',
  share_on_linkedIn: 'Share on LinkedIn',

  badges_point_system: 'Points System',
  badges_beside_gaining_reputation:
    'Besides gaining reputation with your questions and answers, you receive badges for being especially helpful. Badges appears on your profile page, questions & answers.',
  badges_points_for_a_new: 'Points for a new user in the community.',
  badges_choosing_the_best: 'Choosing the best answer for a question.',
  badges_add_an_answer: 'Add an answer in the community.',
  badges_voting_a_question: 'Voting a question in the community.',
  badges_following_a_user: 'Following a user in the community.',
  badges_voting_an_answer: 'Voting an answer in the community.',
  badges_badges_system: 'Badges System',
  badges_pundit: 'Pundit',
  badges_explainer: 'Explainer',
  badges_professional: 'Professional',
  badges_enlightened: 'Enlightened',
  badges_you_must_have: 'You must have a total score of',
  badges_in_at_least: 'in at least',
  badges_non_community_wiki:
    'non-community wiki answers to achieve this badge. Highest scoring answer that outscored an accepted answer with score of more than',

  mainpage_recent_question : 'Recent Questions',
  mainpage_most_answerd: 'Most Answered',
  mainpage_most_visited:'Most Visited',
  mainpage_most_voted: 'Most Voted',
  mainpage_no_answers: 'No Answers',
  mainpage_danang_vietnam : 'Da nang, Viet Nam',
  mainpage_load_more_questions: 'Load More Questions',

  login_thank_to_login_to_continue: 'Thank to login to continue'
};
